<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Funiculars website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Funiculars website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homedale Village Project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/homedale-village-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/homedale-village-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been working on a small project involving my hometown&amp;rsquo;s commercial centre, Homedale village. Historically it used to be Wainuiomata&amp;rsquo;s main commercial centre but in more recent history it has become rundown.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My project&amp;rsquo;s goal is to just simply suggest how the village could be redeveloped. I feel that this is necessary to do now more than any time because of the rest of the suburb&amp;rsquo;s development and recent proposals for Puketahā wildlife sanctuary gives the village a unique position as the ecological hub of the Hutt. But what it needs to get there is a proper redevelopment that brings modernity and community to the village.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Development is an utter mess</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/webdevmess/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/webdevmess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started learning HTML and CSS a decade ago, 2015. Back in intermediate school my teacher introduced me to a tool known as &lt;a href=&#34;https://neocities.org/&#34;&gt;neocities&lt;/a&gt;. I started using it obsessively to express and to present &lt;a href=&#34;https://neocities.org/site/valuesforkids&#34;&gt;things&lt;/a&gt; in my class. And over the next decade I stuck to neocities for the benefits that it gave to me for free. But I&amp;rsquo;ve always desired my own website domain and learning how to make a website &amp;ldquo;professionally&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
